About a year and a half ago, I quit my
job, moved to the countryside, and
started a new life.
Since then, I've learned quite a few
lessons on how to cultivate a feeling of
abundance while living simply.
I grew up moving quite a bit. I lived in
multiple different countries and
traveled to even more.
When I moved here without any plans to
move or travel again in the future,
it was a cathartic experience
in which I had to redefine what it was
to live a meaningful life.
True fulfillment doesn't come from the
acquisition of material things,
nor is it acquired through traveling,
visiting new places, and constantly
having new exciting experiences.
It's a little more complicated than
that, I find.
It's part of the life journey in which
we continue to discover what it is that
makes us happy.
There is no easy cure for sadness.
Instead, I find that to cultivate joy,
you must treat it like a seed.
You must take care of it and let it grow
and watch over it.
And sometimes it doesn't produce the
abundance that you were hoping for.
But with time, maybe next year, it will.
The key is to know that things don't
ever stay the same for long.
The seasons change and so will you.
It's impossible to predict where your
life will be in the future.
I could have never predicted that I
would be here.
City life was overwhelming to my more
sensitive, quiet spirit and I longed to
move to the countryside.
It wasn't until I came here that I
realized how crucial one's environment
is to their creativity
and their mental health.
Living in a rural area did not solve my
lack of fulfillment, but it did create a
foundation
in which I could start to build up my
courage
to live my life how I wanted instead of
comparing it to that of others.
I'd never realized how oppressing it was
to live by someone else's standards
until I came here.
Over time, I got back in touch with what
it is that makes me truly happy.
The day-to-day experiences and joys of
simple living.
I no longer needed to travel or to
acquire things in order to feel as if my
life was a success.
Instead, the sweet smell of calendula
tea
was enough to make my day just about
perfect.
For example,
I take care of young children as my
primary job
and spending time with them and
experiencing the world through their
eyes
constantly reminds me to change my
perspective
and see the little moments of life as
what is truly meaningful and what is
truly living.
I am constantly surprised how my new
lifestyle ignites my creativity.
Not only do I enjoy painting and reading
and writing,
but I am trying all types of new skills
and crafts.
While we often covet the ability to
travel the world at a whim,
I find that there is long-lasting
fulfillment from learning new skills and
experimenting with new ideas.
I hope this video brought you some
peaceful thoughts.
I'm not offering solutions to anyone's
difficulties.
I'm just simply sharing the little
things that I've learned
through living in a rural area
on how to cultivate a feeling of
abundance
in a society that often focuses on
scarcity
and negativity.
There is so much joy to be had in this
world.
And while we can recognize the darkness,
we must make sure to also encourage the
light in our own hearts.